{
    "id": "d5896f1787fb432ba4f8787b222bd833",
    "title": "Infinitives and -ing forms exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "952554c20d4e43df9057f8d05aa0781f",
            "title": "Infinitives And Ing Forms",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I hate the idea …………………………. old.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to get",
                        "of getting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The thought ……………………….. never entered his head.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to fail",
                        "of failing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is very good ………………………. problems.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to solve",
                        "at solve",
                        "at solving"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am tired …………………………. to advice.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to listen",
                        "of listening"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "A strimmer is a machine ………………………….. grass and weeds.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to cut",
                        "for cutting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I must find something ………………………. that fly.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to kill",
                        "for killing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am proud …………………………… won.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "of having",
                        "to have",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "You can’t make an omelette without …………………….. eggs.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to break",
                        "breaking",
                        "to breaking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I look forward to ……………………………… from you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hear",
                        "hearing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am not used to ……………………………. in London.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "drive",
                        "driving"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}